How come you're taking
Asuka-senpai's handouts to her?
What does it matter?
You don't have practice
because of the rain, right?
Come with me, girl.
You're asking me to be your girl?
Let's get going.
Misaki-senpai, my answer is obviously "yes"!
Your answer is surely up in the sky!
This voice...
Break through the darkness
and the endless world...
Asuka?
She's singing.
May your wishes shine eternal,
Master of the Heavens, Zephyrion!
Episode Nine:
The Answer is Up in the Sky!
I feel like I wasted my time.
That was the Zephyrion theme song.
What's Zephyrion?
A mecha anime that aired when we were kids.
The weak, no-good
protagonist—wait for it—
What?
becomes invincible when he pilots Zephyrion!
It's from Asuka.
"Thanks for bringing me the handouts.
My mother passed them on to me.
Sorry for not noticing you came by."
Could I borrow that for a second?
Why?
"You were singing Zephyrion's
theme song just now, weren't you?"
Let's Zephyr it sometime.
She replied.
"Sure! Zeph, zeph!"
"Zeph, zeph"? Seriously, what?
I think she's saying, "Yes, yes."
That's not what I mean. I guess
I had nothing to worry about.
Good morning!
Oh, morning.
You seem fine. Thank goodness.
I am. Sorry for making you worry.
Misaki-chan, thank you for yesterday.
No problem. Morning.
Sorry I couldn't make it to
practice yesterday, New Captain.
Don't be. It was rained out, anyway.
And could you drop the "new" already?
Morning.
Good morning, Coach.
Are you all right, Asuka?
Yes. Sorry to have worried you.
Think you can practice today?
Yeah, I'm totally good.
Bring it on, I say!
You don't have to get that worked up.
Asuka really is different.
No! Bring it on, I say!
Compared to me.
You just recovered, so take it easy.
You think?
No, no!
I don't think I'll last five hours without
falling asleep if I don't get worked up!
Sounds like you, all right.
A-Asuka-senpai?
S-Sorry. I can't fly too well.
Fix your posture and try to fly straight.
O-Okay!
Uh, try a high yo-yo next.
Okay!
Try a low yo-yo next, then.
O-Okay!
Asuka?!
I wonder what's wrong with her.
Come here, Asuka.
Coming!
Asuka-chan.
Sorry. I'm no good at all.
Seriously. It's like you've
lost your save data.
Yeah...
I wonder why.
Just do some stretches and call it a day.
Coach...
Try doing some image
training once you get home.
Picture yourself flying correctly.
And give it another shot tomorrow.
Got it.
Good-bye!
I'm sorry.
Well, they say even the best
athletes go through slumps.
Even when I try to light
a fire and stand up again,
I'm only reminded of my weakness.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Zephyrion?
Where are you from? Are you lost?
I'm...
I'm not lost.
Then what?
I'm a crying, sulking, weak, and no-good girl.
Isn't that line from Zephyrion?
Let's play together, then.
Come on, let's go.
Right...
You're leaving already?
Yeah.
But we'd just become friends...
You can have this.
But...
Just take it!
Thanks!
Relax. That part was already broken.
Whatcha doing?
I heard you couldn't fly,
but you got here just fine.
Misaki-chan...
Hup.
Here, your lunch. You
left it in the classroom.
Th-Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're not wearing it, huh?
That hairpin.
For some reason,
I felt like I shouldn't.
My wings might not have been my own.
I've wanted to fly ever
since I was a little child.
I wanted to change the weak,
no-good girl that I was.
So when I came to this island and
got to fly for the first time,
I was really happy.
I picked up FC, practiced with all I had,
and met a lot of amazing people.
I had so much fun.
I found Inui-san's FC incredible, too.
The fact that someone was
capable of doing that
made me feel I could soar even higher.
But I was just getting
carried away, wasn't I?
I couldn't do a thing in
my match against Inui-san.
I hadn't changed at all. I was still
the weak, no good girl I'd always been.
The wings that gave me flight until now,
I'd just borrowed from you and Coach.
So I got scared of my weakness...
...and you couldn't fly anymore, huh?
I see.
Practicing by myself feels so pointless.
What can ya do? Asuka-chan said
she wanted to keep image training.
Notice of Absence
Kurashina Asuka
Mashiro
Asuka-senpai is taking time
off from the team! (>口<;)
Mashiro
Her mother phoned
and said she wasn't home yet!
Asuka...
To Asuka
Where are you now?
Please respond!
Misaki
Tobisawa
Uh...
What am I doing here?
What're you talking about?
You were the one standing outside my
house with a blank look on your face.
Well...
I wanted to reply to your
message, but my battery ran out.
I didn't know what to do,
and before I realized...
It's just like you to show
up to respond in person.
Y'know...
Why are you even here, Mashiro?
That's because you told me
Asuka-senpai was at your place.
So I rushed here as soon as I could.
I most definitely am not here to
take advantage of the situation
to sample your home cooking!
Sorry to have worried you.
Let's just eat.
Yeah, let's eat!
Let's eat.
I tried making gyoza tonight.
With flying fish dumplings
and lots of flyer stock.
It's great!
Your flying fish gyoza made
with love is just divine!
There was no love involved.
Th-This is...
...delicious, right?
It's really good.
Asuka.
Y-Yes?
Stay the night.
"S-Stay"...
Misaki-senpai...
I'll gladly be your personal hug Mashillow.
Could you hurry up and eat?
I need to clean up.
Got it!
Wait, Senpai!
No, you can't!
Please...
Sheesh.
Listen, I'm sorry.
I ended up causing you trouble.
No problem, I guess.
Why?
Why are you taking time off?
Well...
What about you?
Me?
I...
A total stud, no matter how
many times I look at it!
Get lost, Mashiro.
What? Am I not welcome here?
I feel like an abandoned cat right now.
Yeah, I'm abandoning you.
Ack!
Fine. Since I'm such a bother,
I'll get out of your way now.
Shoo, shoo.
You two feel free to flirt
to your hearts' content.
Where did she even pull
these pictures out from?
I wanna see, too!
Hey, wait.
Who is this boy?
Me.
I'm sorry.
I often got mistaken for
a boy, so I'm used to it.
Grav-Shoes?
I got them as a birthday gift.
I was so happy, I kept
flying around by myself.
After a point, that couldn't
satisfy me anymore,
so I challenged random people to matches.
You look like you were having fun.
But I get bored easily, you see.
Before I knew it, I stopped
caring about Flying Circus.
After you showed up, I started
playing again on a whim.
But this time,
I ran away.
I thought I'd put up a good
fight against Shindou-san,
but I really hadn't.
He got serious against you, though.
I was so upset.
I couldn't understand why.
And then he lost the match against Inui-san.
I didn't want to believe it.
"What does that make me?" I wondered.
And I got scared.
But you...
You said it was incredible.
I couldn't understand you.
I felt like you were out of my league.
And even after losing so badly, Shindou-san
hadn't let it get to him at all.
In fact, it'd only made him more motivated.
Because the fear of losing something
shows that you enjoy it.
I can't enjoy that sort of thing.
That's why
I decided to quit.
Misaki-chan...
What can you even say?
I'm so pathetic.
That's not true!
You're awesome!
Sorry.
Asuka?
I mean,
you're the one who took me
to the world in the sky.
Looking at your pretty flying form made
me wish I could fly like that, too.
Th-Thanks.
Oh, no need.
You'll be fine.
I know you're flying with your own wings.
Not that I have proof, though.
You don't?
Wow, it's really late.
Shall we turn in?
Yes.
I'm Mashiro, the abandoned cat.
I guess they're not coming to pick me up.
Jeez.
Not that I blame them.
Fly across the starry sky
with your unrivaled wings.
Your answer is surely up in the sky.
Break through the darkness
and the endless world.
May your wishes shine eternal,
Master of the Heavens, Zephyrion!
You two forgot about my
existence, didn't you?
Oh, is that so?
You were in your own little world, huh?
Gee, sorry for being the fifth
wheel—Are you even listening to me?
Sorry, Mashiro-chan.
Well, it's fine.
Step on it, or we'll be late!
I know!
H-Hey!
What is it? Less talking, more sprinting!
Misaki-chan!
Wh-What?
Take me on...
in a match!
Asuka-senpai?
The answer is up in the sky!
Wait, that was just a leave letter?
Yes. I wanted to take a day off.
And you, Misaki?
I'm gonna play Asuka in a match now.
If I lose, I'll come back.
"The answer is up in the sky"?
You're too naïve, Asuka.
The only things that are up
there are victory and defeat.
And I'm gonna win, no matter what.
I'll give it all I've got.
To be honest, I'm a bit
scared of taking Asuka on.
If I win, Misaki-chan will
come back to the team.
I can't lose here.
On your marks...
Set!
She can fly again!
She must've remembered her way of flying.
Point to Asuka-senpai!
Here I go!
You're not getting past me!
What?!
Let's zipzap, Misaki-chan!
Asuka, that's my catchphrase!
Point to Misaki-senpai 1—
1-2!
That won't get it done!
Point to Misaki-senpai. 1-3.
Misaki-chan really is amazing.
But I won't be
outdone!
Point to Asuka-senpai!
Let's roll, Asuka!
Okay!
They're so high up.
Is that Delta Force?!
Did Asuka use it on the spur of the moment?!
You know, I've realized something.
I was scared because I'd found
something to take seriously—
something to dedicate myself
to—for the first time.
And I think I'm still a little scared.
You?
The only thing on my mind...
is to look up and fly.
I really do think the
answer is up in the sky.
It may well be.
Misaki-senpai...
You won. What are you going to do with this?
Notice of Withdrawal
Got a pen?
Here.
Thanks.
That should do it.
Notice of Withdrawal
Registration
I'm not "coming back."
I'm rejoining.
Ah.
So you're our newest member!
Oh, I guess.
Call me "Mashiro-senpai" from now on.
In your dreams.
Fly across the starry sky
with your unrivaled wings
Oh, so this is Jephyrion?
Your answer is surely up in the sky
You're not pronouncing it right,
Senpai. You can't Zephyr like that.
So that wing of yours was Jephyrion's, Asuka?
Break through the darkness
and the endless world
You're still not pronouncing it right.
A boy from this island gave
it to me when I was a child.
May your wishes shine eternal,
Master of the Heavens, Zephyrion!
A boy from this island?
Who could it be?
Like a female version of Coach.
Gross!
Well, it was a long time ago.
Wait, I think I once played a
similar kid in an FC match.
Maybe it was the same person?
Who knows?
To Be Continued
And who cares?
Preview
Our FC is beautiful.
6 AM? Seriously?
Coach?!
Is that for FC, too?
Episode Ten:
Is That For FC, Too?